Let's do the first task.
最初のタスクを実行しましょう
We're going to rename the number input parameter to have a different name.
numberインプットパラメータの名前を 変更します
This is the first input parameter, int number,
これは最初のインプットパラメータの int numberです
and all I need to do is just change the variable name.
しなくてはならないのは ただ単純に 変数の名前を変えるだけです
I'm going to change this to, for example, numberOfCoffees.
たとえばこれを numberOfCoffeesに 変更してみましょう
It can be any name that you want.
好きな名前にすることができます
Now, I immediately see a warning and an error.
さて 警告とエラーがすぐに 表示されます
The warning says, the parameter numberOfCoffees is never used,
警告は numberOfCoffeesという パラメータは使用されていないと言っています
because nowhere in this method do I use this variable.
このメソッドのどこでも この変数を 使用していないためです
Then I see that there's an error that says, cannot resolve symbol number.
次に numberというシンボルを解決できません というエラーが表示されています
Now, there's no variable called number.
numberと呼ばれる変数はありません
There's no local variable called number.
numberと呼ばれるローカル変数はありません
There's no global variable called number.
numberと呼ばれる グローバル変数はありません
And it's not an input parameter, either.
これはインプットパラメータでもありません
instead, I need to switch this so that it's called numberOfCoffees.
代わりに これがnumberOfCoffeesと呼ばれるように 変更する必要があります
And there you go, that fixed the error.
これで エラーが修正されました
So I'm going to run it on my device now.
これを私の機器で実行してみます
And this is what it looks like.
このようになります
The quantity picker works as expected.
量の選択は期待通りに動作します
There should be no visible change to the user because we just modified
インプットパラメータの名前を変更したので ユーザーに対して目に見える変更は
the name of an input parameter.
一切ありません
Also, we didn't have to change the way that the method is being called.
また メソッドが呼び出される方法を変更する 必要もありませんでした
We can still say displayQuantity and then pass in anything we want.
それでも displayQuantityと呼び 好きなものを渡すことができます
It doesn't matter to the caller what this input parameter name is.
呼び出し元にとってはインプットパラメータの 名前は問題ではありません
The second task is to change the data type of the input parameter
第二のタスクはインプットパラメータの データ型を変更することです
from int to string.
intからstringに変えます
So in the display quantity method, I'm going to change the input so
displayQuantityメソッドでは インプットを変更して
that instead of a integer data type, it expects a string data type, like this.
整数のデータ型の代わりに このように 文字列のデータ型を求めるようにします
And now, there's a couple errors in our app.
私たちのアプリには いくつかのエラーが 発生しています
When I scroll up, I see that there is a red squiggly underline
上にスクロールすると 赤でくねくねとした 下線があることに気が付きます
in the increment method and in the decrement method.
incrementメソッドと decrementメソッドの部分です
The error message says,
エラーメッセージいわく
displayQuantity string in MainActivity can't be applied to something int.
MainActivity内のdisplayQuantity文字列は intのものには適用することができないということです
What it's saying is that we can't pass the quantity variable into
これはつまり 量の変数をメソッドへと 渡すことはもうできないということであり
the method anymore because this is an integer, and it's expecting a string.
これは整数ですが 文字列が求められているためです
This mismatch in data type is causing an error, and
データ型のミスマッチがエラーを 引き起こしています
the app won't even run on our device.
それで私たちの機器ではアプリが動作しないのです
This is a compile time error.
これはコンパイルタイムエラーです
There's a couple ways to fix this.
これを直す方法がいくつかあります
Either we have to change what's being passed into the method so
これが実際には文字列となるように メソッドへと渡されるものを
that this is actually a string.
変更する必要があります
I could put 100 here and put it in double quotes so that it's a string, and
ここに100を渡し 二重引用符に入れ これが文字列となるようにし
that would match the right input type here.
適切なインプット型とマッチするように することができます
But what we really want is for quantity to still be an integer so
ですが 私たちが実際に求めているのは 量を整数のままに保ち
that we can do math on it to increase it by one or decrease it by one.
1ずつ増加または減少できるように 計算できるようにすることです
So I'm going to leave this as quantity.
これは量のままにしておきます
And then this should be changed to be an integer.
そして これは整数へと 変更されるべきですね
And then our app should work again.
私たちのアプリはまた動作するようになるはずです
Cool. So so
良し それなりですね
far, we've seen an example of a method with one input parameter.
インプットパラメータ1つのメソッドに 関する例を見てきました
But what about examples of methods with zero input parameters, or
ですがインプットパラメータがゼロだったり 2つやそれ以上のインプットパラメータを持つ
two input parameters, or more?
メソッドの例はどうでしょうか？